{"1":[
    {
        "answer": "union",
        "question": "There are currently 50 states, which are bound together in a __________ with each other.",
        "similar_words": [
            "adhocracy",
            "affiliate",
            "alliance",
            "association",
            "blue",
            "bureaucracy",
            "company",
            "defense"
        ],
        "title": "U.S. state => Analyzing 'U.S. States'",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/U.S._state"
    },
    {
        "answer": "governmental jurisdiction",
        "question": "Each state holds __________ __________ over a defined geographic territory and shares its sovereignty with the United States federal government.",
        "similar_words": [],
        "title": "U.S. state",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/U.S._state"
    },
    {
        "answer": "sovereignty",
        "question": "Due to the shared __________ between each state and the federal government, Americans are citizens of both the federal republic and of the state in which they reside.",
        "similar_words": [
            "home rule",
            "local option"
        ],
        "title": "U.S. state",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/U.S._state"
    },
    {
        "answer": "state citizenship",
        "question": "__________ __________ and residency are flexible, and no government approval is required to move between states, except for persons covered by certain types of court orders (e.g., paroled convicts and children of divorced spouses who are sharing custody).",
        "similar_words": [],
        "title": "U.S. state",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/U.S._state"
    },
    {
        "answer": "range",
        "question": "States __________ in population from just under 600,000 (Wyoming) to over 39 million (California), and in area from 1,214 square miles (3,140 km2) (Rhode Island) to 663,268 square miles (1,717,860 km2) (Alaska).",
        "similar_words": [
            "area",
            "coverage",
            "depth",
            "frontage",
            "length",
            "limit",
            "scope"
        ],
        "title": "U.S. state",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/U.S._state"
    },
    {
        "answer": "use",
        "question": "Four states __________ the term commonwealth rather than state in their full official names.",
        "similar_words": [
            "acting",
            "aid",
            "attempt",
            "behavior",
            "behavior",
            "burst",
            "buzz",
            "calibration"
        ],
        "title": "U.S. state",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/U.S._state"
    },
    {
        "answer": "governmental authority",
        "question": "States are divided into counties or county-equivalents, which may be assigned some local __________ __________ but are not sovereign.",
        "similar_words": [],
        "title": "U.S. state",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/U.S._state"
    },
    {
        "answer": "structure varies",
        "question": "County or county-equivalent __________ __________ widely by state.",
        "similar_words": [],
        "title": "U.S. state",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/U.S._state"
    },
    {
        "answer": "power",
        "question": "State governments are allocated __________ by the people (of each respective state) through their individual constitutions.",
        "similar_words": [
            "ability",
            "accuracy",
            "accuracy",
            "air",
            "amorality",
            "appearance",
            "arability",
            "asset"
        ],
        "title": "U.S. state",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/U.S._state"
    },
    {
        "answer": "government",
        "question": "All are grounded in republican principles, and each provides for a __________, consisting of three branches: executive, legislative, and judicial.",
        "similar_words": [],
        "title": "U.S. state",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/U.S._state"
    },
    {
        "answer": "number",
        "question": "States possess a __________ of powers and rights under the United States Constitution.",
        "similar_words": [
            "critical mass",
            "decrease",
            "increase",
            "insufficiency",
            "margin",
            "negativity",
            "positivity",
            "quantity"
        ],
        "title": "U.S. state",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/U.S._state"
    },
    {
        "answer": "bicameral legislature",
        "question": "States and their residents are represented in the United States Congress, a __________ __________ consisting of the Senate and the House of Representatives.",
        "similar_words": [],
        "title": "U.S. state",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/U.S._state"
    },
    {
        "answer": "total number",
        "question": "Each state is also entitled to select a number of electors (equal to the __________ __________ of representatives and senators from that state) to vote in the Electoral College, the body that directly elects the President of the United States.",
        "similar_words": [],
        "title": "U.S. state",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/U.S._state"
    },
    {
        "answer": "time",
        "question": "Over __________, the Constitution has been amended, and the interpretation and application of its provisions have changed.",
        "similar_words": [
            "humiliation",
            "piece"
        ],
        "title": "U.S. state",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/U.S._state"
    },
    {
        "answer": "general tendency",
        "question": "The __________ __________ has been toward centralization and incorporation, with the federal government playing a much larger role than it once did.",
        "similar_words": [],
        "title": "U.S. state",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/U.S._state"
    },
    {
        "answer": "debate",
        "question": "There is a continuing __________ over states' rights, which concerns the extent and nature of the states' powers and sovereignty in relation to the federal government and the rights of individuals.",
        "similar_words": [
            "argument",
            "conference",
            "deliberation",
            "negotiation",
            "panel discussion",
            "postmortem",
            "public discussion"
        ],
        "title": "U.S. state",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/U.S._state"
    },
    {
        "answer": "authority",
        "question": "The Constitution grants to Congress the __________ to admit new states into the Union.",
        "similar_words": [
            "corporatism",
            "hold",
            "iron fist",
            "rein"
        ],
        "title": "U.S. state",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/U.S._state"
    },
    {
        "answer": "establishment",
        "question": "Since the __________ of the United States in 1776, the number of states has expanded from the original 13 to 50.",
        "similar_words": [
            "activation",
            "attack",
            "constitution",
            "face-off",
            "first step",
            "groundbreaking",
            "housing start",
            "icebreaker"
        ],
        "title": "U.S. state",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/U.S._state"
    },
    {
        "answer": "question",
        "question": "The Constitution is silent on the __________ of whether states have the power to secede (withdraw) from the Union.",
        "similar_words": [
            "challenge",
            "interrogation"
        ],
        "title": "U.S. state",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/U.S._state"
    }
],
"2": [
  {
      "answer": "metropolitan area",
      "question": "The __________ __________ of France extends from the Mediterranean Sea to the English Channel and the North Sea, and from the Rhine to the Atlantic Ocean.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "France",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/France"
  },
  {
      "answer": "country 's",
      "question": "The country's 18 integral regions (five of which are situated overseas) span a combined area of 643,801 square kilometres (248,573 sq mi) which, as of October 2017, has a population of 67.15 million people.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "France",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/France"
  },
  {
      "answer": "semi-presidential republic",
      "question": "France is a unitary __________ __________ with its capital in Paris, the country's largest city and main cultural and commercial centre.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "France",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/France"
  },
  {
      "answer": "area",
      "question": "Rome annexed the __________ in 51 BC, and held the region until 486, when the Germanic Franks conquered the region and formed the Kingdom of France.",
      "similar_words": [
          "antipodes",
          "backwater",
          "biogeographical region",
          "breadbasket",
          "district",
          "domain",
          "field",
          "field"
      ],
      "title": "France",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/France"
  },
  {
      "answer": "european power",
      "question": "France emerged as a major __________ __________ in the Late Middle Ages following its victory in the Hundred Years' War (1337 to 1453).",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "France",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/France"
  },
  {
      "answer": "french culture",
      "question": "During the Renaissance, __________ __________ flourished and a global colonial empire was established, which by the 20th century would be the second largest in the world.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "France",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/France"
  },
  {
      "answer": "16th",
      "question": "The __________ century was dominated by religious civil wars between Catholics and Protestants (Huguenots).",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "France",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/France"
  },
  {
      "answer": "power",
      "question": "France became Europe's dominant cultural, political, and military __________ under Louis XIV.",
      "similar_words": [
          "ability",
          "accuracy",
          "accuracy",
          "air",
          "amorality",
          "appearance",
          "arability",
          "asset"
      ],
      "title": "France",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/France"
  },
  {
      "answer": "18th",
      "question": "In the late __________ century, the French Revolution overthrew the absolute monarchy, established one of modern history's earliest republics, and saw the drafting of the Declaration of the Rights of Man and of the Citizen, which expresses the nation's ideals to this day.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "France",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/France"
  },
  {
      "answer": "19th",
      "question": "In the __________ century Napoleon took power and established the First French Empire, whose subsequent Napoleonic Wars shaped the course of continental Europe.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "France",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/France"
  },
  {
      "answer": "collapse",
      "question": "Following the __________ of the Empire, France endured a tumultuous succession of governments culminating with the establishment of the French Third Republic in 1870.",
      "similar_words": [
          "ague",
          "amyloidosis",
          "anuresis",
          "catastrophic illness",
          "condition",
          "decompression sickness",
          "disease",
          "food poisoning"
      ],
      "title": "France",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/France"
  },
  {
      "answer": "major participant",
      "question": "France was a __________ __________ in World War I, from which it emerged victorious, and was one of the Allied Powers in World War II, but came under occupation by the Axis powers in 1940.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "France",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/France"
  },
  {
      "answer": "liberation",
      "question": "Following __________ in 1944, a Fourth Republic was established and later dissolved in the course of the Algerian War.",
      "similar_words": [
          "arrival",
          "attainment",
          "base on balls",
          "beachhead",
          "cakewalk",
          "close call",
          "credit",
          "face saver"
      ],
      "title": "France",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/France"
  },
  {
      "answer": "day",
      "question": "The Fifth Republic, led by Charles de Gaulle, was formed in 1958 and remains to this __________.",
      "similar_words": [
          "attosecond",
          "bell",
          "femtosecond",
          "half-hour",
          "hour",
          "mean time",
          "microsecond",
          "millisecond"
      ],
      "title": "France",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/France"
  },
  {
      "answer": "global centre",
      "question": "France has long been a __________ __________ of art, science, and philosophy.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "France",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/France"
  },
  {
      "answer": "number",
      "question": "It hosts Europe's third-largest __________ of cultural UNESCO World Heritage Sites and receives around 83 million foreign tourists annually, the most of any country in the world.",
      "similar_words": [
          "critical mass",
          "decrease",
          "increase",
          "insufficiency",
          "margin",
          "negativity",
          "positivity",
          "quantity"
      ],
      "title": "France",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/France"
  },
  {
      "answer": "country",
      "question": "France is a developed __________ with the world's fifth-largest economy by nominal GDP and ninth-largest by purchasing power parity.",
      "similar_words": [
          "amphictyony",
          "cell",
          "Holy Roman Empire",
          "lobby",
          "lunatic fringe",
          "Palestine National Authority",
          "revolutionary group",
          "state"
      ],
      "title": "France",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/France"
  },
  {
      "answer": "household wealth",
      "question": "In terms of aggregate __________ __________, it ranks fourth in the world.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "France",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/France"
  },
  {
      "answer": "education",
      "question": "France performs well in international rankings of __________, health care, life expectancy, and human development.",
      "similar_words": [
          "acting",
          "aid",
          "attempt",
          "behavior",
          "behavior",
          "burst",
          "buzz",
          "calibration"
      ],
      "title": "France",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/France"
  },
  {
      "answer": "great power",
      "question": "France remains a __________ __________ in the world, being one of the five permanent members of the United Nations Security Council with the power to veto and an official nuclear-weapon state.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "France",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/France"
  },
  {
      "answer": "member state",
      "question": "It is a leading __________ __________ of the European Union and the Eurozone.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "France",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/France"
  },
  {
      "answer": "member",
      "question": "It is also a __________ of the Group of 7, North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO), Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development (OECD), the World Trade Organization (WTO), and La Francophonie.",
      "similar_words": [
          "adjunct",
          "affiliate",
          "ally",
          "bedfellow",
          "collaborator",
          "colleague",
          "colleague",
          "participant"
      ],
      "title": "France => Analyzing 'France'",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/France"
  }
],
"3": [
  {
      "answer": "'s mainland",
      "question": "The country__________ __________ is bordered to the south and east by the Mediterranean Sea except for a small land boundary with Gibraltar; to the north and northeast by France, Andorra, and the Bay of Biscay; and to the west and northwest by Portugal and the Atlantic Ocean.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "Spain",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spain"
  },
  {
      "answer": "european country",
      "question": "It is the only __________ __________ to have a border with an African country (Morocco) and its African territory accounts for nearly 5% of its population, mostly in the Canary Islands but also in Ceuta and Melilla.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "Spain",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spain"
  },
  {
      "answer": "area",
      "question": "With an __________ of 505,990 km2 (195,360 sq mi), Spain is the largest country in Southern Europe, the second largest country in Western Europe and the European Union, and the fourth largest country in the European continent.",
      "similar_words": [
          "antipodes",
          "backwater",
          "biogeographical region",
          "breadbasket",
          "district",
          "domain",
          "field",
          "field"
      ],
      "title": "Spain",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spain"
  },
  {
      "answer": "population",
      "question": "By __________, Spain is the sixth largest in Europe and the fifth in the European Union.",
      "similar_words": [
          "age group",
          "ancients",
          "baffled",
          "blind",
          "blood",
          "brave",
          "business people",
          "chosen people"
      ],
      "title": "Spain",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spain"
  },
  {
      "answer": "capital",
      "question": "Spain's __________ and largest city is Madrid; other major urban areas include Barcelona, Valencia, Seville, Bilbao and M\u00e1laga.",
      "similar_words": [
          "accounts receivable",
          "credit",
          "crown jewel",
          "deep pocket",
          "equity",
          "funds",
          "hole card",
          "intangible"
      ],
      "title": "Spain",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spain"
  },
  {
      "answer": "peninsula",
      "question": "Iberian cultures along with ancient Phoenician, Greek and Carthaginian settlements developed on the __________ until it came under Roman rule around 200 BCE, after which the region was named Hispania, based on the earlier Phoenician name Sp(a)n or Spania.",
      "similar_words": [
          "archipelago",
          "beachfront",
          "cape",
          "coastal plain",
          "floor",
          "foreland",
          "forest",
          "island"
      ],
      "title": "Spain",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spain"
  },
  {
      "answer": "independent realms",
      "question": "At the end of the Western Roman Empire the Germanic tribal confederations in migration from Central Europe invaded the Iberian peninsula and established themselves in relatively __________ __________ in its western provinces, including the Sueves, Alans and Vandals.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "Spain",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spain"
  },
  {
      "answer": "kingdom",
      "question": "The Visigothic __________ fell to the Moors except in the north where shortly after started a process known as Reconquista.",
      "similar_words": [
          "distaff",
          "front",
          "lap",
          "political arena",
          "preserve",
          "province"
      ],
      "title": "Spain",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spain"
  },
  {
      "answer": "country",
      "question": "Spain emerged as a unified __________ in the 15th century under the Catholic Monarchs, who completed the eight centuries-long Reconquista in 1492.",
      "similar_words": [
          "amphictyony",
          "cell",
          "Holy Roman Empire",
          "lobby",
          "lunatic fringe",
          "Palestine National Authority",
          "revolutionary group",
          "state"
      ],
      "title": "Spain",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spain"
  },
  {
      "answer": "modern period",
      "question": "In the early __________ __________, Spain became one of history's first global empires, leaving a vast cultural and linguistic legacy that includes over 500 million Hispanophones, making Spanish the world's second most spoken native language, after Mandarin Chinese.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "Spain",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spain"
  },
  {
      "answer": "parliamentary democracy",
      "question": "Spain is a __________ __________ and constitutional monarchy, with King Felipe VI as head of state.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "Spain",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spain"
  },
  {
      "answer": "country",
      "question": "It is a major developed __________ with the world's fourteenth largest economy by nominal GDP and sixteenth largest by purchasing power parity.",
      "similar_words": [
          "amphictyony",
          "cell",
          "Holy Roman Empire",
          "lobby",
          "lunatic fringe",
          "Palestine National Authority",
          "revolutionary group",
          "state"
      ],
      "title": "Spain",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spain"
  },
  {
      "answer": "member",
      "question": "It is a __________ of the United Nations (UN), the European Union (EU), the Eurozone, the Council of Europe (CoE), the Organization of Ibero-American States (OEI), the Union for the Mediterranean, the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO), the Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development (OECD), OSCE, the Schengen Area, the World Trade Organization (WTO) and many other international organisations.",
      "similar_words": [
          "adjunct",
          "affiliate",
          "ally",
          "bedfellow",
          "collaborator",
          "colleague",
          "colleague",
          "participant"
      ],
      "title": "Spain",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spain"
  },
  {
      "answer": "permanent invitation",
      "question": "Spain has a \"__________ __________\" to the G20 summits that occur generally once a year.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "Spain => Analyzing 'Spain'",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spain"
  }
],
"4": [
  {
      "answer": "square kilometres",
      "question": "Covering approximately 9.6 million __________ __________ (3.7 million square miles), it is the third- or fourth-largest country by total area, depending on the source consulted.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "China",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/China"
  },
  {
      "answer": "neighbor countries",
      "question": "China also has the most __________ __________ in the world.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "China",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/China"
  },
  {
      "answer": "exercises jurisdiction",
      "question": "Governed by the Communist Party of China, it __________ __________ over 22 provinces, five autonomous regions, four direct-controlled municipalities (Beijing, Tianjin, Shanghai, and Chongqing), and the special administrative regions of Hong Kong and Macau.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "China",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/China"
  },
  {
      "answer": "world 's",
      "question": "China emerged as one of the world's earliest civilizations, in the fertile basin of the Yellow River in the North China Plain.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "China",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/China"
  },
  {
      "answer": "millennia",
      "question": "For __________, China's political system was based on hereditary monarchies, or dynasties, beginning with the semi-legendary Xia dynasty in 21st century BCE.",
      "similar_words": [
          "air alert",
          "bimester",
          "bimillennium",
          "bout",
          "bronze age",
          "calendar day",
          "calendar month",
          "century"
      ],
      "title": "China",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/China"
  },
  {
      "answer": "3rd",
      "question": "In the __________ century BCE, the Qin unified core China and established the first Chinese dynasty.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "China",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/China"
  },
  {
      "answer": "dynasty",
      "question": "The succeeding Han __________ saw some of the most advanced technology at that time, including papermaking and the compass, along with agricultural and medical improvements.",
      "similar_words": [
          "homefolk",
          "house",
          "name",
          "people"
      ],
      "title": "China",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/China"
  },
  {
      "answer": "inventions",
      "question": "The invention of gunpowder and printing in the Tang dynasty completed the Four Great __________.",
      "similar_words": [
          "fecundity",
          "flight",
          "genius",
          "imagination",
          "invention",
          "inventiveness"
      ],
      "title": "China",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/China"
  },
  {
      "answer": "Tang",
      "question": "__________ culture spread widely in Asia, as the new maritime Silk Route brought traders to as far as Mesopotamia and Somalia.",
      "similar_words": [
          "hotness",
          "nip",
          "pungency"
      ],
      "title": "China",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/China"
  },
  {
      "answer": "rule",
      "question": "Dynastic __________ ended in 1912 with the Xinhai Revolution, as a republic replaced the Qing dynasty.",
      "similar_words": [
          "abstraction",
          "category",
          "conceptualization",
          "fact",
          "hypothesis",
          "law",
          "law",
          "lexicalized concept"
      ],
      "title": "China",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/China"
  },
  {
      "answer": "country",
      "question": "The Chinese Civil War led to the break up of the __________ in 1949, with the victorious Communist Party of China founding the People\u2019s Republic of China on the mainland while the losing Kuomintang retreated to Taiwan, a dispute which is still unresolved.",
      "similar_words": [
          "amphictyony",
          "cell",
          "Holy Roman Empire",
          "lobby",
          "lunatic fringe",
          "Palestine National Authority",
          "revolutionary group",
          "state"
      ],
      "title": "China",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/China"
  },
  {
      "answer": "introduction",
      "question": "Since the __________ of economic reforms in 1978, China's economy has been one of the world's fastest-growing.",
      "similar_words": [
          "activation",
          "attack",
          "constitution",
          "face-off",
          "first step",
          "groundbreaking",
          "housing start",
          "icebreaker"
      ],
      "title": "China",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/China"
  },
  {
      "answer": "second-largest economy",
      "question": "As of 2016, it is the world's __________ __________ by nominal GDP and largest by purchasing power parity (PPP).",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "China",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/China"
  },
  {
      "answer": "world 's",
      "question": "China is also the world's largest exporter and second-largest importer of goods.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "China",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/China"
  },
  {
      "answer": "weapons state",
      "question": "China is a recognized nuclear __________ __________ and has the world's largest standing army and second-largest defense budget.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "China",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/China"
  },
  {
      "answer": "permanent member",
      "question": "The PRC is a member of the United Nations, as it replaced the ROC as a __________ __________ of the UN Security Council in 1971.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "China",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/China"
  },
  {
      "answer": "member",
      "question": "China is also a __________ of numerous formal and informal multilateral organizations, including the WTO, APEC, BRICS, the Shanghai Cooperation Organization (SCO), the BCIM and the G20.",
      "similar_words": [
          "adjunct",
          "affiliate",
          "ally",
          "bedfellow",
          "collaborator",
          "colleague",
          "colleague",
          "participant"
      ],
      "title": "China",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/China"
  },
  {
      "answer": "great power",
      "question": "China is a __________ __________ and a major regional power within Asia, and has been characterized as a potential superpower.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "China => Analyzing 'China'",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/China"
  }
],
"5": [
  {
      "answer": "northeast",
      "question": "Turkey is bordered by eight countries with Greece and Bulgaria to the northwest; Georgia to the __________; Armenia, the Azerbaijani exclave of Nakhchivan and Iran to the east; and Iraq and Syria to the south.",
      "similar_words": [
          "cardinal compass point",
          "east by north",
          "east by south",
          "east northeast",
          "east southeast",
          "north by east",
          "north by west",
          "north northeast"
      ],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "country",
      "question": "The __________ is encircled by seas on three sides with the Aegean Sea to the west, the Black Sea to the north, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south.",
      "similar_words": [
          "amphictyony",
          "cell",
          "Holy Roman Empire",
          "lobby",
          "lunatic fringe",
          "Palestine National Authority",
          "revolutionary group",
          "state"
      ],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "form",
      "question": "The Bosphorus, the Sea of Marmara, and the Dardanelles, which together __________ the Turkish Straits, divide Thrace and Anatolia and separate Europe and Asia.",
      "similar_words": [
          "anagram",
          "anaphor",
          "antonym",
          "back-formation",
          "charade",
          "classifier",
          "cognate",
          "content word"
      ],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "capital",
      "question": "Ankara is the __________ while Istanbul is the country's largest city and main cultural and commercial centre, classified as a leading global city.",
      "similar_words": [
          "accounts receivable",
          "credit",
          "crown jewel",
          "deep pocket",
          "equity",
          "funds",
          "hole card",
          "intangible"
      ],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "minority",
      "question": "Kurds are the largest __________ at about 15-20% of the population, and other ethnic minorities include Circassians, Albanians, Arabs, Bosniaks and Laz.",
      "similar_words": [
          "body",
          "congregation",
          "force",
          "fringe",
          "gathering",
          "interest",
          "Jewry",
          "kin"
      ],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "official language",
      "question": "The __________ __________ is Turkish, which is the most widely spoken Turkic language in the world.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "today",
      "question": "Minority languages spoken __________ in Turkey include Kurmanji, Bosnian, Laz, Albanian, Arabic, Zaza, Kabardian and several others.",
      "similar_words": [
          "date",
          "here and now",
          "now",
          "time being",
          "tonight"
      ],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "area",
      "question": "The __________ of Turkey has been inhabited since the Paleolithic age by various ancient Anatolian civilisations, as well as Assyrians, Greeks, Thracians, Phrygians, Urartians and Armenians.",
      "similar_words": [
          "antipodes",
          "backwater",
          "biogeographical region",
          "breadbasket",
          "district",
          "domain",
          "field",
          "field"
      ],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "area",
      "question": "After Alexander the Great conquered these lands, the __________ was Hellenized, a process which continued under the Roman Empire and its transition into the Byzantine Empire.",
      "similar_words": [
          "antipodes",
          "backwater",
          "biogeographical region",
          "breadbasket",
          "district",
          "domain",
          "field",
          "field"
      ],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "area",
      "question": "The Seljuk Turks began migrating into the __________ in the 11th century, and their victory over the Byzantines at the Battle of Manzikert in 1071 symbolizes the start and foundation of Turkey.",
      "similar_words": [
          "antipodes",
          "backwater",
          "biogeographical region",
          "breadbasket",
          "district",
          "domain",
          "field",
          "field"
      ],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "invasion",
      "question": "The Seljuk Sultanate of R\u00fbm ruled Anatolia until the Mongol __________ in 1243, when it disintegrated into small Turkish beyliks.",
      "similar_words": [
          "breakthrough",
          "foray",
          "infiltration",
          "interpenetration"
      ],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "end",
      "question": "From the __________ of the 13th century the Ottomans started uniting Turkish principalities in Anatolia and then went on to create an empire that encompassed much of Southeast Europe, West Asia and North Africa.",
      "similar_words": [
          "boundary",
          "extreme point",
          "limit"
      ],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "world power",
      "question": "The Ottoman Empire became a __________ __________ beginning with the reign of Suleiman the Magnificent, reaching a golden age in the early modern period.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "18th",
      "question": "It remained powerful and influential for two more centuries, until important setbacks in the __________ and 19th century forced it to cede strategic territories in Europe, which signalled the loss of its former military strength and wealth.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "coup",
      "question": "After the 1913 Ottoman __________ d'\u00e9tat, which effectively put the country under the control of the Three Pashas, the Ottoman Empire decided to join the Central Powers during World War I.",
      "similar_words": [
          "action",
          "assembly",
          "attendance",
          "brainstorming",
          "communalism",
          "competition",
          "confederation",
          "conflict"
      ],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "war",
      "question": "During the __________, the Ottoman government committed genocides against its Armenian, Assyrian and Pontic Greek subjects.",
      "similar_words": [
          "amphibious landing",
          "battle",
          "blockade",
          "defense",
          "electronic warfare",
          "police action",
          "resistance",
          "saber rattling"
      ],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "war",
      "question": "Following the __________, the conglomeration of territories and peoples that formerly comprised the Ottoman Empire was partitioned into several new states.",
      "similar_words": [
          "amphibious landing",
          "battle",
          "blockade",
          "defense",
          "electronic warfare",
          "police action",
          "resistance",
          "saber rattling"
      ],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "abolition",
      "question": "The Turkish War of Independence, initiated by Mustafa Kemal Atat\u00fcrk and his colleagues against occupying Allies, resulted in the __________ of monarchy in 1922 and the establishment of the Republic of Turkey in 1923, with Atat\u00fcrk as its first president.",
      "similar_words": [
          "abort",
          "abortion",
          "adjournment",
          "closure",
          "completion",
          "deactivation",
          "demonetization",
          "destruction"
      ],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "philosophy",
      "question": "Atat\u00fcrk enacted numerous reforms, many of which incorporated various aspects of western thought, __________, and customs into the new form of Turkish government.",
      "similar_words": [
          "autotelism",
          "conviction",
          "doctrine",
          "expectation",
          "faith",
          "fetishism",
          "geneticism",
          "individualism"
      ],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "charter member",
      "question": "Turkey is a __________ __________ of the UN, an early member of NATO, the IMF and the World Bank, and a founding member of the OECD, OSCE, BSEC, OIC and G-20.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "associate member",
      "question": "After becoming one of the first members of the Council of Europe in 1949, Turkey became an __________ __________ of the EEC in 1963, joined the EU Customs Union in 1995 and started accession negotiations with the European Union in 2005 which have been effectively stopped by the EU in 2017 due to \"Turkey\u2019s path toward autocratic rule\".",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "economy",
      "question": "Turkey's __________ and diplomatic initiatives led to its recognition as a transcontinental regional power while its location has given it geopolitical and strategic importance throughout history.",
      "similar_words": [
          "body",
          "dragnet",
          "ecosystem",
          "judiciary",
          "language system",
          "machinery",
          "network",
          "nonlinear system"
      ],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "century",
      "question": "In the 21st __________, Turkey is a middle power and has the world's 17th largest economy by nominal GDP, as well as the 13th largest by PPP, out of 191 countries measured by IMF.",
      "similar_words": [
          "air alert",
          "bimester",
          "bimillennium",
          "bout",
          "bronze age",
          "calendar day",
          "calendar month",
          "clotting time"
      ],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "substantial actor",
      "question": "As a __________ __________ in several industrial sectors, it is the world's 28th largest exporter and 21st largest importer of goods.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "cultural history",
      "question": "Well known for its rich __________ __________, Turkey has contributed significantly to arts, music, literature, sports, and science and technology.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "7th",
      "question": "Turkey is the __________ most popular country as a tourist destination in Europe, attracting 25.4 million international tourists in 2016.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "current administration",
      "question": "Turkey's __________ __________ headed by president Tayyip Erdo\u011fan has reversed many of the earlier reforms, such as Freedom of the Press, a Legislative System of Checks and Balances, and a set of standards for secularism in government, as previously enacted by Atat\u00fcrk.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  },
  {
      "answer": "parliamentary republic",
      "question": "Turkey is a secular, unitary, __________ __________; slated to transition to a presidential system in 2019, following a 2017 referendum.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "Turkey",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey"
  }
],
"6": [
  {
      "answer": "north-western coast",
      "question": "Lying off the __________ __________ of the European mainland, the United Kingdom includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland and many smaller islands.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "United Kingdom",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Kingdom"
  },
  {
      "answer": "part",
      "question": "Northern Ireland is the only __________ of the United Kingdom that shares a land border with another sovereign state\u200d\u2014\u200cthe Republic of Ireland.",
      "similar_words": [
          "affinity",
          "association",
          "business relation",
          "causality",
          "change",
          "comparison",
          "connection",
          "control"
      ],
      "title": "United Kingdom",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Kingdom"
  },
  {
      "answer": "area",
      "question": "With an __________ of 242,500 square kilometres (93,600 sq mi), the United Kingdom is the 78th-largest sovereign state in the world and the 11th-largest in Europe.",
      "similar_words": [
          "antipodes",
          "backwater",
          "biogeographical region",
          "breadbasket",
          "district",
          "domain",
          "field",
          "field"
      ],
      "title": "United Kingdom",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Kingdom"
  },
  {
      "answer": "populous country",
      "question": "It is also the 21st-most __________ __________, with an estimated 65.5 million inhabitants.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "United Kingdom",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Kingdom"
  },
  {
      "answer": "constitutional monarchy",
      "question": "The United Kingdom is a __________ __________ with a parliamentary democracy.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "United Kingdom",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Kingdom"
  },
  {
      "answer": "monarch",
      "question": "The __________ is Queen Elizabeth II, who has reigned since 6 February 1952.",
      "similar_words": [
          "chancellor",
          "president",
          "President of the United States",
          "Prime Minister",
          "sovereign"
      ],
      "title": "United Kingdom",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Kingdom"
  },
  {
      "answer": "capital",
      "question": "The __________ of the United Kingdom and its largest city is London, a global city and financial centre with an urban area population of 10.3 million, the fourth-largest in Europe and second-largest in the European Union.",
      "similar_words": [
          "accounts receivable",
          "credit",
          "crown jewel",
          "deep pocket",
          "equity",
          "funds",
          "hole card",
          "intangible"
      ],
      "title": "United Kingdom",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Kingdom"
  },
  {
      "answer": "countries\u2014England",
      "question": "The United Kingdom consists of four __________, Scotland, Wales and Northern Ireland.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "United Kingdom",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Kingdom"
  },
  {
      "answer": "Man",
      "question": "The nearby Isle of __________, Bailiwick of Guernsey and Bailiwick of Jersey are not part of the United Kingdom, being Crown dependencies with the British Government responsible for defence and international representation.",
      "similar_words": [
          "brachycephalic",
          "caregiver",
          "catch",
          "centrist",
          "character",
          "conservative",
          "dolichocephalic",
          "elder"
      ],
      "title": "United Kingdom",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Kingdom"
  },
  {
      "answer": "kingdom",
      "question": "This meant that the united __________ created in 1707 by the Treaty of Union between England and Scotland encompassed all of Great Britain.",
      "similar_words": [
          "distaff",
          "front",
          "lap",
          "political arena",
          "preserve",
          "province"
      ],
      "title": "United Kingdom",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Kingdom"
  },
  {
      "answer": "state",
      "question": "The Kingdom of Ireland then merged with this __________ in 1801 to form the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Ireland.",
      "similar_words": [
          "borough",
          "canton",
          "city",
          "commune",
          "country",
          "county",
          "county palatine",
          "department"
      ],
      "title": "United Kingdom",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Kingdom"
  },
  {
      "answer": "present formulation",
      "question": "Five-sixths of Ireland seceded from the UK in 1922, leaving the __________ __________ of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "United Kingdom",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Kingdom"
  },
  {
      "answer": "height",
      "question": "These are the remnants of the British Empire which, at its __________ in the 1920s, encompassed almost a quarter of the world's land mass and was the largest empire in history.",
      "similar_words": [
          "fourth dimension",
          "length",
          "thickness",
          "thinness",
          "third dimension",
          "width"
      ],
      "title": "United Kingdom",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Kingdom"
  },
  {
      "answer": "british influence",
      "question": "__________ __________ can be observed in the language, culture and legal systems of many of its former colonies.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "United Kingdom",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Kingdom"
  },
  {
      "answer": "country",
      "question": "The United Kingdom is a developed __________ and has the world's sixth-largest economy by nominal GDP  and ninth-largest economy by purchasing power parity.",
      "similar_words": [
          "amphictyony",
          "cell",
          "Holy Roman Empire",
          "lobby",
          "lunatic fringe",
          "Palestine National Authority",
          "revolutionary group",
          "state"
      ],
      "title": "United Kingdom",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Kingdom"
  },
  {
      "answer": "high-income economy",
      "question": "The UK is considered to have a __________ __________ and is categorised as very high in the Human Development Index, ranking 16th in the world.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "United Kingdom",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Kingdom"
  },
  {
      "answer": "world 's",
      "question": "It was the world's first industrialised country and the world's foremost power during the 19th and early 20th centuries.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "United Kingdom",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Kingdom"
  },
  {
      "answer": "great power",
      "question": "The UK remains a __________ __________ with considerable economic, cultural, military, scientific and political influence internationally.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "United Kingdom",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Kingdom"
  },
  {
      "answer": "weapons state",
      "question": "It is a recognised nuclear __________ __________ and is seventh in military expenditure in the world.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "United Kingdom",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Kingdom"
  },
  {
      "answer": "permanent member",
      "question": "The UK has been a __________ __________ of the United Nations Security Council since its first session in 1946.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "United Kingdom",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Kingdom"
  },
  {
      "answer": "member state",
      "question": "It has been a leading __________ __________ of the EU and its predecessor, the European Economic Community (EEC), since 1973.",
      "similar_words": [],
      "title": "United Kingdom",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Kingdom"
  },
  {
      "answer": "member",
      "question": "The UK is also a __________ of the Commonwealth of Nations, the Council of Europe, the G7 finance ministers, the G7 forum, the G20, NATO, the Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development (OECD), and the World Trade Organization (WTO).",
      "similar_words": [
          "adjunct",
          "affiliate",
          "ally",
          "bedfellow",
          "collaborator",
          "colleague",
          "colleague",
          "participant"
      ],
      "title": "United Kingdom",
      "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Kingdom"
  }
]

}

